nexperia.com 2017-06-06

# Privacy Policy | Nexperia

### Privacy Policy

**Privacy**  
NEXPERIA believes strongly in protecting the privacy of the personally identifiable information you share with us. We also believe it is important to inform you about how we will use your personal data, and to give you choices about how those data will be used. By using NEXPERIA's website, you are consenting to NEXPERIA's collection, use, or storage of your personally identifiable information unless you opt out of such collection, use, or storage in accordance with the opt out process described in this Privacy Policy. Therefore, we encourage you to read this Privacy Policy carefully. 

**Scope of this privacy policy**  
In general, this Privacy Policy applies to all personal information of individuals collected or used by NEXPERIA or its subsidiaries. This includes information from websites for commercial use that are owned by NEXPERIA and offline collections of personal data for commercial use owned by NEXPERIA. However, some of our websites or data collections work with special kinds of data which require a somewhat different privacy policy. Whenever and wherever that is the case, NEXPERIA will make it clear that the privacy policy concerned is different from this general NEXPERIA Privacy Policy.

**Why should you share your personal data with Nexperia?  **

Sharing your personally identifiable information enables us to offer you a number of benefits. It will make it easier and more convenient for you to:

  * Register your purchase so you can receive all the benefits to which your purchase entitles you
  * Request information specific to your interests
  * Participate in online communities
  * Receive personalized messages and special offers that are relevant to your interests
  * Save time by storing your preferences
  * Buy NEXPERIA products online
  * Apply for employment

It will also allow us to conduct market research to help us develop better products, to provide more responsive customer service, and to improve our websites.

You may choose to share your information with us in a number of ways online, such as completing an registration form to become a member of MyNexperia, ordering a product, entering a contest, registering a purchase, participating in a promotion, subscribing to a newsletter,  
or submitting information in connection with a job application.

You can also share your personally identifiable information with us by communicating with one of our customer care representatives by e-mail, telephone, or in writing.

Sometimes NEXPERIA obtains your personal data from other parties outside NEXPERIA. This includes the buying of a business of which you already are a customer or the disclosure of your personal data by one of our partner companies. If you do not want us to use your personal data which you have not provided to us yourself, you can let us know by contacting us at the address listed below.

**Sharing information**  
We want to know you better so we can serve you better. But the choice of whether you want this kind of service is up to you.

You should know that your personally identifiable information may be transferred from your home country to other NEXPERIA companies around the world, who may communicate with you about our products or special offers you may find useful. If you do not want us to send you personalized offers or information, you can let us know by checking the appropriate box in the subscription center.

NEXPERIA may share your personally identifiable information with companies that assist NEXPERIA in providing its services such as, but not limited to, IT and communications services, fulfilling orders, analyzing data, sending e-mail, providing marketing assistance and providing customer service. These companies have access to the personally identifiable information needed to perform their services, but shall not  
be entitled to use the information for other purposes.

Furthermore NEXPERIA may share your data with third parties outside NEXPERIA in the following circumstances: Sometimes NEXPERIA sells you a product or offers you a service in a joint marketing effort with other companies. In such cases, your personal data will be shared with these companies. We will always let you know that such relationship exists and who these companies are prior to your registration. Note that these companies often have their own privacy policies that apply to the way they use your personal data. These privacy policies sometimes differ from the NEXPERIA Privacy Policy. NEXPERIA sometimes uses outside companies for handling your purchase or request or for processing your data. NEXPERIA requires these companies to adequately safeguard your personal data and not use your data for any other purpose not authorized by NEXPERIA.

NEXPERIA sometimes sells a business to another company. Such transfer of ownership could include the transfer of your personal data directly related to that business to the buyer. NEXPERIA will release personally identifiable information if compelled by law. NEXPERIA will not sell or provide your personal data to other third parties allowing them to use your personal data for their own purposes.

NEXPERIA will not share any personal financial information you provide (such as credit card information) with other parties unless this is needed to handle your order, process our invoice, or prevent or combat fraud.  
In connection with completing a job application, whether advertised on NEXPERIA’s website or otherwise, you may provide us with information about yourself. We may use this information throughout NEXPERIA in order consider you for employment purposes. If you would like to have information submitted in connection with a job application removed from our system prior to that time, please contact us and live chat with our support team to request your account to be deleted.

From time to time, this Web Site may provide links to other websites.  
You should carefully review the privacy policies on those sites; they may differ from the NEXPERIA Privacy Policy.

NEXPERIA will solely disclose personally identifiable information for the purposes as described in this Privacy Policy and in case disclosure is necessary according to applicable law.

**"Cookies" and website logging**  
Some of our Web Sites will send a "cookie," a small text file, to your computer. This allows us to recognize your computer the next time you visit, without bothering you with another request to register. If you do not wish to receive cookies, please refer to the “Help” file of your Internet Browser to learn how to either block all cookies or receive a warning before a cookie is stored. To learn more about cookies we encourage you to visit www.cookiecentral.com

If you visit our Web Sites to browse, read, or download information,  
we collect and store some “visitor information” from you, such as the name of the domain and host from which you access the Internet, the Internet Protocol (IP) address of the computer you are using, the date and time you access our Web Site, and the Internet address of the website from which you linked directly to our Web Site. We use this information to measure the traffic on our Web Sites and to help us make our Web Sites more useful. We delete this information after some time.

**Safeguarding the information you share with us**  
We recognize our responsibility to protect the information you entrust to us. NEXPERIA takes all reasonable precautions to keep personally identifiable information secure. Any third party that NEXPERIA shares such information with shall be required to do the same.  NEXPERIA uses a variety of secure techniques to protect your information, including secure servers, firewalls, and encryption of financial data;

NEXPERIA websites also may make chat rooms, forums, message boards and/or newsgroups available to you. Please remember that any personally identifiable information you provide in these areas is also available to other users. It is your responsibility to protect the personally identifiable information you provide in these areas, and you should exercise caution before deciding to disclose it.

**Your rights**  
Once you have provided us with your personally identifiable information, you will have reasonable access to that information so you can change or delete it. You may do this by accessing your online profile, or by requesting a copy of your profile at the contact address listed below.

Because NEXPERIA sells thousands of products in hundreds of countries, you may have previously provided us with personally identifiable information through reply cards, our call centers, or in some other manner. Your decision not to register now will not affect the information you have already provided to NEXPERIA. Of course, you will always have the option to unsubscribe to any online contact from NEXPERIA or change your personal profile information.

**Data retention**  
The personally identifiable information that NEXPERIA collects will only be retained for as long as required for the purposes which it was collected or by applicable law. 

**Special information for parents & guardians**  
While NEXPERIA Web Sites are generally not targeted at children under the age of thirteen, it is NEXPERIA policy to comply with the law when it requires that a parent's or guardian's permission is secured before knowingly collecting, using, or disclosing personal information from children under the age of thirteen.

We strongly recommend that parents take an active role in supervising the online activity of their children.

**Social media**  
NEXPERIA may add blogs, message boards, community forums,  
chat rooms, social media channels or similar communities (each a "Community") to the Web Site from time to time. NEXPERIA cannot be held responsible for any use or misuse by third parties if you choose to share personally identifiable information in a Community.

NEXPERIA may also provide links to other web sites including social media platforms. NEXPERIA makes no representation or warranties regarding how any personally identifiable information is used or stored by these third parties. We recommend reviewing the privacy policies of such third parties.

**Changes to privacy policy**  
NEXPERIA reserves the right to from time to time make changes to the Privacy Policy. Any updated versions will be posted on the NEXPERIA website. NEXPERIA will give reasonable notice of any material changes Please visit the website frequently to monitor changes.

**Contacting us**  
You may contact us if you would like to:

  * ask us any question regarding our privacy policy
  * request a copy of your personal data, or change or delete your  
personal data
  * opt-out from receiving any future personalized offers or information from NEXPERIA

**Our address**  
You can find our address by pressing the Contact Us link at the bottom of this Web Site.
